Finding Aid for the Sidney Reznick Papers PASC.0297
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Sound recordings, 1947-1968
  - "Sez Who!" #75, 1958 December 21 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #76, 1958 December 28 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #77, 1959 January 4 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Robert Mitchum Album "Ballad of Thunder Road" "my Honey's Lovin Arms", undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Robinhood, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - "Chattanooga Cha Cha", undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - "Chattanooga Cha Cha", undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    (2 recordings)
  - "Mr. Bankroll", undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - "Mr. Bankroll", undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Vaugh Monroe record album "Westward Ho, the Wagons!" "Wringle Wrangle", undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Eddie Bracken - Some of My Friends are Birds (Parts 1 and 2), undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - "Young Mr Gabriel" Voice Test, 1946 August 16 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Revised: "Sez Who?" Record (Acetate), undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 June 25 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - CBS Radio "Sez Who?", 1953 May 25 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - "What Would You Have Said?", undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Jack Paar Show (Excerpts), undated (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - "Three on a Honeymoon" Starring Phil Baker, undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Hearing is Believing, 1953 May 25 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - "Young Voice", undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - 80 Musical Stories, Games, and Songs, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - "Who, He?", undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Based on "Sez Who"
  - "Sez Who?" Starring Henry Morgan, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - T.S., undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - "Who, He?" (Voices), undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - "Three on a Honeymoon" Starring Phil Baker (Revised), undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - "Who, He?", undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - "The Other Woman", 1968 August 6 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - "The Other Woman", 1968 August 8 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - "The Other Woman", 1968 August 1 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - "Sez Who?" Starring Henry Morgan, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Series 3: Photographs, undated (Box 93)
  Photographs include signed photographs, photographs of Morning Show staff, and photographs of staff on set.